[{"answer": "Don't sell yourself short. You made all the flight arrangements, hotels, buses", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Summer-of-George.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "So, when you actually did work, what it was that you did", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Why didn't you ask me? I know a million theater jokes. 'What's the deal with those guys down in the pit?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Summer-of-George.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "It's a funny observation.", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Severance package...The that place are giving me three months full pay for doing nothing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Summer-of-George.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I'm really going to do something with these three months", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I'll just squeeze in..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Summer-of-George.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "My job. What are you doing?", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yeah, when I went to pick her up there was this dude", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Summer-of-George.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "What do you think it could've been just some dude", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Hey Kramer", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Summer-of-George.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "How's that my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I can't do this", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Summer-of-George.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "He's not doing anything. Goodbye", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "So listen, I'm going to crab a bite to eat at that place. You wanna go", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Summer-of-George.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "The Tony is taking me to my friend's.", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Eh, what", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Summer-of-George.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Oh yeah, my friend? ", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Sure", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Summer-of-George.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "The one with the..", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "No, I'll crab it.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Summer-of-George.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What, did you lose your remote", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Not", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Summer-of-George.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No, because that's..", "qsentId": 24}]